|How old are you?|
|Job title|
|What industry do you work in?|
|If your job title needs additional context, please clarify here:|
|What is your annual salary? (You'll indicate the currency in a later question. If you are part-time or hourly, please enter an annualized equivalent -- what you would earn if you worked the job 40 hours a week, 52 weeks a year.)|
|How much additional monetary compensation do you get, if any (for example, bonuses or overtime in an average year)? Please only include monetary compensation here, not the value of benefits.|
|Please indicate the currency|
|If "Other," please indicate the currency here: |
|If your income needs additional context, please provide it here:|
|What country do you work in?|
|If you're in the U.S., what state do you work in?|
|What city do you work in?|
|How many years of professional work experience do you have overall?|
|How many years of professional work experience do you have in your field?|
|What is your highest level of education completed?|
|What is your gender?|
|What is your race? (Choose all that apply.)|
